

903-293-6594

Gmail LinkedIn GitHub Twitter Portfolio Blog

## SKILLS:

Front-end Web Development; knockoutJS; jasmineJS; FTP; Sublime Social Media Management; Written Communication; Personnel Development Course Development; Instructional Design; Content Production; Team Building Teaching; Tutoring; Training; Marketing; Critical Thinking; Research; Hiring PowerPoint; Video Recording; Video Editing; iMovie; Life Long Learner

## **SUMMARY:**

I have reached for the heights of management in the fast-paced world of business and elevated the math skills of middle school children as principal of a small private school. Most recently, I produced content as a freelance writer. I renewed my studies after anticipating the need for website development skills and am excited to be part of the evolving field of user experience design and interface development.

## EXPERIENCE:

Online Profile Reviewer Udacity: Remote

Jun 2015 - Current

I am one of the first profile reviewers with Udacity. I review documents based on a rubric and offer actionable and helpful feedback to students.

**Web Developer** *Freelancer: Janesville, WI* May 2015 - Current As a front-end developer I write <u>object-oriented programming</u> in <u>javaScript</u>, and use <u>HTML</u>, CSS, jQuery and Bootstrap to design responsive websites that provide positive user experiences. Projects include a <u>single page application</u> using Google Maps and FourSquare APIs, and an <u>optimized</u> website using PageSpeed Insights.

**Exec Content Director** *Urban Gaming Elite: Milwaukee, WI* Aug 2014 – Jun 2015 I worked closely with the founder to build a <u>community</u> of inclusive gamers in the Midwest region who were bound by their love for community and creativity. I edited and created images with Photoshop, used MS Office to create Word and Excel documents and shared files with freelancers on Google Drive. I co-managed our social media accounts and networked with regional organizers for partnership opportunities.

## **EDUCATION:**

Udacity	Front-End Web Development Nanodegree	2014 - 2015
The Second City	Improvisational Acting, Comedic Writing	2012 - 2013
Texas A&M University	Bachelor of Applied Arts & Sciences	2008 - 2010
Texarkana College	Associate in Business Marketing	2004 - 2007